《指定幸存者》前情提要
Previously on "Designated Survivor"...
艾尔萨卡并非国会爆炸案的真凶
埃布·莱纳德指出艾尔萨卡不是
Abe Leonard asserts Al-Sakar was not responsible
柯克曼面临艾尔萨卡事件难题
袭击国会大厦的罪魁祸首
for the attack of the Capitol.
我们已经身处狼穴了  总统先生
The jackals are at the door, Mr. President.
我觉得我们快知道真相了
I think we're really close to cracking this thing.
你的首席探员失踪了
Your lead investigator is missing.
试图杀你的人依旧活着
The man who tried to kill you is still alive.
白宫里的叛徒身份依然成谜
And the mole in the White House remains unknown.
我要解除你的权力  即刻生效
I am relieving you of your command, effective immediately.
-什么  -将军  你被撤职了
- What? - General, you are fired.
你杀了我的亲人
You kill my family...
我也杀你的
I kill yours.
杰森
Jason...
奏效了
It's all working.
所有人的注意力都在联调局那边  而非我们
Everyone's focused on the FBI, not us.
汉娜在哪
Where is Hannah?
出外勤了
On assignment.
打开所有的集装箱进行搜索
I want every container opened and searched.
约翰·埃德加·胡佛联调局大楼
车库二层
手放在脑后  手放在脑后
Get your hands behind your head! Hands behind your head!
跪在地上  快
On the ground right now!
手举过头顶  跪下
Hands above your head! Get on your knees!
-你们不明白  -快  跪下
- You don't understand! - Now! On the ground!
手放在我能看到的地方
Put your hands where I can see them!
跪在地上  快点
Get on the ground! Do it!
-好吧  -跪下
- Okay. - Get on your knees!
跪下  我不会再说第二次了
I said get on the ground! I'm not gonna ask you again!
退后  不然我就引爆炸弹
Get back, or I'll detonate it!
退后  不然我就炸了这里
Get back, or I'll blow it!
把枪放下  我是认真的
Put your guns down! I mean it!
停  不准开火  退后
Stop. Nobody fires. Get back!
退后
Get back!
快追
Go, go!
去后面  上楼
Go back! Up the stairs!
■
让开
Get out of the way!
快啊
Come on!
别动  让我看到你的双手  别动
Freeze! Let me see your hands! Hold it right there!
指定幸存者
第一季 第二十一集
[本季终]
总统先生
Mr. President.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
有什么消息
What have you got?
联调局把她拘留了
The FBI has her in custody.
我要尽快见她
I want to talk to her as soon as possible.
翻译     苏小黛   murky不知道改什么  薇薇安
是  总统先生
Yes, sir.
我已经说过了  我跟这事没关系
I already told you -- I had nothing to do with this.
翻译     一只虾  silence 长颈鹿  pang  Michael
我在车后座醒过来
I woke up in the back of the van --
我们在你公寓发现的图纸怎么解释
What about the schematics we found in your apartment --
翻译     子V爱学习  小玫瑰·咕嘟鸡  酥ki酱  星星与野狗
车库的结构图
the structural blueprints to the garage?
你把车停在了承重梁正下方
You parked your van right under a load-bearing beam,
校对     苏小黛  胖鹿牵走早巨哈哈哈哈  小早只为看MQ
如果你想炸毁大楼
which is exactly where you'd want to park
就必须把车停在那里
if you want to take the building down.
汉娜
Hannah.
时间轴     姜姜  浪影抱住Seth小天使  Avis要看早巨的P
幸好你没事
Thank God you're okay.
马上解开她的手铐
Get those cuffs off her right now.
她是这起恐怖袭击的主要嫌犯
She's a lead suspect in a terrorist attack.
后期     虫虫不咬人
-是才怪  放了她  -谁授命的
- The hell she is. Let her go. - Under whose authority?
美国总统
The president of the United States.
说得和真的似的
Yeah, right.
总统想要马上见她
He wants her in his office ASAP.
总监     MQ小早
嗯
Yeah.
丹  白宫打给我了
Dan, I got the White House on the line.
公告     人人影视永久官方网站 www.YYeTs.com
你刚才说什么来着
You were saying?
你还好吗
You all right?
他们杀了杰森
They killed Jason.
我们得向总统汇报我们所了解的情况
All right, we have to tell the president what we know.
他们想陷害我发动恐袭
They wanted to blame me for an attack,
所以他们伪造了放在我公寓里的证据
so they planted evidence in my apartment.
他们通知了联调局
They called the FBI,
告诉他们我带着炸弹去了车库
said that I'd be in the garage with a bomb.
我们在审问从货轮上抓到的嫌疑人
We're interrogating the suspects that we arrested on the freighter.
他们供出了窝点
They're giving up Intel on the cells.
劳埃德那边怎么样了
What about Lloyd?
我们找到的唯一联系是
The only link that we've managed to find
货轮归布朗宁·里德旗下
is between the ship and
一间已倒闭的子公司所有
a defunct subsidiary of Browning Reed.
证据还不够充分
It's not a smoking gun.
那又怎样  汤姆  你得逮捕那混蛋
So what? You need to bring that bastard in, Tom.
我也同意
I agree, sir.
如果不能定他罪的话
There's no point in bringing him in today
抓他根本没有意义
if we have to let him out tomorrow.
我们得像对付麦克利什那样对付他
We need to play this the same way that we did MacLeish.
结果呢
Well, look how that turned out.
长官
Sir?
我同意他们的观点
I agree with them.
特别是现在我们不知道
Especially given the fact that we don't know
白宫里面的叛徒是谁
who the traitor is in the White House.
去抓他吧
Bring him in.
我们的目标是帕特里克·劳埃德
Our target is Patrick Lloyd.
我们认为他是国会爆炸案的幕后主使
We believe that he is responsible for the bombing on our Capitol.
他现在住在位于弗吉尼亚州沃伦顿西边
He currently resides on a 100-acre horse farm
一处100英亩的养马场里
west of Warrenton, Virginia.
我们要假定他全副武装
We should assume he is heavily armed.
他杀了我们的朋友  杀了我们的领袖
He killed our friends, and he killed our leaders.
我们要活捉他
We will take him alive,
并让他对我们的所作所为付出代价
and we will make him pay for everything he took from us.
大家都清楚了吗
Is everyone clear on that?
清楚了
Yes.
好的  我们出发
All right. Let's move out.
柯克曼政府存在着联调局阴谋吗
Is there an FBI conspiracy in the Kirkman Administration?
这令人感到不安  奈特  十分不安
It's very concerning, Nate -- very concerning.
目前的已知信息
I mean, what we now know,
使我们对总统所说的一切都产生了怀疑
it casts doubt on everything the president has ever told us.
我们还怎么能信任他
How are we supposed to trust him?
请进
Come in.
有什么消息了
What have you got?
目前我们已确认位于蒙大纳  亚利桑那
So far, we've identified cells in Montana, Arizona,
宾州  新泽西和新墨西哥州的窝点
Pennsylvania, New Jersey, and New Mexico.
联调局的境内威胁联合反恐部队
Now, the FBI's Joint Terrorism Task Force on Domestic Threats
已派小队前往这些地点以便协调突击
is moving teams into position so we can coordinate the raids,
避免惊动他们
not tip them off.
我读了他们的宣言
You know, I read their "manifesto."
真是太荒唐了
It was ridiculous.
他们引用的历史警句恰到好处
They use just the right amount of historical quotes
以试图正当化自己的所作所为
to try and make themselves sound legitimate.
这与党派无关
They're not political.
这是对权力的攫取  一场未遂的政变
This is a power grab -- an attempted coup.
劳埃德那边处理得怎么样了
Where are we at with Lloyd?
战术部队已经出发了
Tactical team's en route.
我们很快就能将他拿下
We'll have him in custody within the hour.
一有消息立刻通知我
I want updates as soon as they come in.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
干得漂亮  法索局长  谢谢
Great work, Director Foerstel. Thank you.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
这论点很出彩  鲍曼议员
That's an excellent argument, Senator Bowman,
但我觉得下一位嘉宾可能会反对你的观点
but I'm sure my next guest will probably disagree --
联调局掩盖了真相吗  柯克曼沉默了
有请白宫前幕僚长亚伦·肖尔
recent White House chief of staff Aaron Shore.
谢谢  奈特
Thank you, Nate.
你想对担心存在政府阴谋论的
So, what do you say to all the Americans out there
美国人民说些什么
who are worried about a government conspiracy?
我会说柯克曼总统大概是
I'd say that President Kirkman is
我认识的人里面最诚实的一位了
probably the most honest man I've ever met.
我认为你和鲍曼议员
And I think you and Senator Bowman
都试图将国家安全问题
are both trying to score political points
变成自己的政治筹码
over matters of national security.
你是说报道是假的吗  肖尔先生
Are you saying this story isn't true, then, Mr. Shore?
我是说我了解得并不全面
I'm saying I haven't been fully briefed,
议员也是一样
and neither has the senator,
所以我们中没有一个人有权作出指控
so neither one of us should be making any kind of accusations.
但事实是
Well, the fact remains --
如果涉及了国家安全问题
if these are matters of national security,
总统就应该向公众澄清
the president should just say so.
但至今他什么也没说  这令局势很不利
But so far, he's said nothing. That's a disservice.
我非常了解总统
Knowing the president as well as I do...
没人有权作出指控
我确信即使他的确隐瞒了某些事实
I'm sure if he's holding on to any kind of secret,
那也是为了全美国民众的安危着想
it's for the safety of the American people.
如果说有人在帮倒忙  那也是你才对
If anyone is doing a disservice here, it's you.
敬请大家明天继续收看本节目
Stay tuned tomorrow, folks.
这个故事没有完结
This story's not going anywhere.
-我是摩尔  -我是威尔士
- Moore. - It's Wells.
你看到劳埃德了吗
You have eyes on Lloyd?
看到了  他还在房子里
Yeah, he's still in the house.
好的  很好
All right, good.
原位等待  我们在路上了
Hold your position. We're en route.
收到
Copy.
洛萨诺已拿到包裹  一切就绪
执行任务
威尔士探员
Agent Wells!
这里没人
All clear here.
给我一份布朗宁·里德和其子公司名下
I want a list of every plane, truck, car, ship, helicopter
所有飞机  卡车  汽车和直升机的清单
registered to Browning Reed or their subsidiaries,
而且要立刻追踪到位
and I want it tracked now.
调动联邦航管局
That means FAA,
-州机动车辆管理局  -威尔士探员
- it means state DMV, - Agent Wells!
线上搜索  当地执法部门
it means ATL, law enforcement.
无论用什么手段  马上给我查清楚
Whatever you have to do, you get it done.
-威尔士探员  -什么事
- Agent Wells. - Yeah.
弗吉尼亚州的高速公路巡警
Virginia highway patrol said
发现了一辆登记在劳埃德名下的车辆
they spotted a vehicle registered to Lloyd
在沿州际公路南行
driving south on the interstate.
打开对讲机
Open the walkie.
威尔士探员
Agent Wells!
帕特里克·劳埃德在切萨皮克的交通临检处
I got a Patrick Lloyd sighting at a traffic stop in Chesapeake.
运输安全局的人说
TSA says they got eyes on him
在罗利达勒姆国际机场看到他
over at Raleigh-Durham International.
现在又有报告说
They're now saying his credit card was just used
他刚刚在匹兹堡的汽车站使用过信用卡
at a bus station in Pittsburgh.
查到他的银行卡  在德克萨斯州的布兰诺
I got a hit on his ATM card -- in Plano, Texas.
骗局
Shell game.
去他妈的
Damn it!
大家都在问  下一次的汇报是什么时候
Everyone's asking - when the next briefing is.
在我有料可以爆给他们之前
Well, until I can give them something more than a "No comment,"
我要尽可能地回避媒体
I'm gonna stay away from the press for as long as possible.
事情进展还顺利吗
How's that working out for you?
我要开始锁办公室的门了
And I'm gonna start locking my office door.
锁门也阻碍不了我  相信我
Oh, that's not gonna slow me down. Trust me.
你想干什么  埃布
What do you want, Abe?
我想得到白宫的回应
A White House comment.
我已经回应了你的报道  那就是无可奉告
I already gave your story a "no comment."
这对话是不是似曾相识
Haven't we done this before?
我感觉这像是  旧事重演
I feel like it's, like, "Groundhog Day" with you.
艾尔萨卡是过去的事了
Al-Sakar was yesterday's story.
我说的是将于明天刊登的报道
I'm talking - about tomorrow's edition.
这次"无可奉告"可派不上用场了
A "No comment" Is not gonna cut it this time.
那的确是部好电影
It's a good movie, though.
groundhog day亦指电影《偷天情缘》
总统先生
Mr. President.
得和你说点紧要事  先生
Major flag for you, sir.
什么事
What is it?
埃布·莱纳德在写一篇报道
Abe Leonard is running a story claiming
称联调局副局长杰森·亚特伍德
that FBI Deputy Director Jason Atwood
在总统办公室里因谋杀马吉德·纳萨尔被捕
was arrested in the Oval for the murder of Majid Nassar.
他说白宫把这消息封锁了
He says the White House covered it up.
你觉得我要怎样回应他
I mean, how do you want to respond to this?
跟莱纳德先生说我想见他
Tell Mr. Leonard I want to see him.
抱歉
Sorry?
安排个会议  我要和他面对面谈谈
Set up a meeting -- face-to-face.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我打不通他电话
I can't get through to him.
他要解决掉莱纳德·埃布的报道
He's needs to address the Abe Leonard story.
我明白你想汤姆表现得像一个政治家
I know you want Tom to behave like a politician,
但这样他就不再是他自己了  艾米丽
but that's just not who he is, Emily.
他是美国总统  艾丽克斯
He is the president of the United States, Alex.
他要为白宫争辩
He needs to defend the office.
我知道  他会按他自己的方式来做
Yes, I know, and he will -- in his own way.
你会在这里待多久  约个午餐吧
How long are you in town for? I miss our lunches.
我今晚就要回去了
I got to head back tonight.
我准备跟朋友在海亚当斯酒店随便吃点东西
I'm just gonna grab a bite with a friend at The Hay-Adams.
还有  艾米丽
And, Emily?
一切都会好起来的
It's gonna be okay.
没错
Right.
他是怎样逃掉的
How did he get by us?
不知道
Don't know.
应该是那叛徒通风报信的
The working theory is that the traitor tipped him off.
不幸的是  我们至今还无法找到他
And, unfortunately, we're still no closer to finding him.
我们要冻结他的资产  榨干那混蛋
We need to freeze his assets -- bleed the son of a bitch dry.
联系财政部  我们要起草一项行政命令
Contact Treasury. We'll have an executive order drafted.
-是的  总统先生  -谢谢你
- Yes, sir. - Thank you.
每位总统都要处理一个重大危机
Every president has a defining crisis.
而汤姆  你有好几个呢
You, Tom, have had several.
但是你会经受住这次危机
But you are going to weather this.
因为不管怎样  事情都将接近尾声
Because one way or another, it's all coming to an end.
而与此同时呢
And in the meantime?
为冲击做好准备
Brace for impact.
至少这方面我越来越得心应手了
Well, at least I'm getting better at that.
华盛顿白宫
网络连接提示
正在建立安全连接
需要密码  区分大小写
保密IP路由网络
我是里特
Ritter.
我是恰克  立刻接通汉娜办公室
It's Chuck. Get to Hannah's office now.
马克
法雷尔
美国海军
中尉
无限期
美国军警部门
法雷尔  马克
中尉
怎么了
What is it?
还记得上次的入侵事件吗
Okay, remember the hack
用来传送马吉德·纳萨尔的视频那次
that was used to deliver the Majid Nassar video?
记得  毁了白宫西翼一半的电脑
Yeah. That attack destroyed half the computers in the West Wing.
也留下了一个重要的数据痕迹
Also left behind a serious digital footprint.
那么假设
Now, working under the assumption
这个内鬼也是那次入侵事件的罪魁祸首
that our traitor was responsible for that hack, as well,
我一直在密切关注同一个代码
I've been keeping an eye out for that same code
以防再次有人使用
in case it was used again.
这个内鬼刚刚进入了保密IP路由网络
Our traitor just accessed SIPRNET.
五角大楼吗  为什么
The Pentagon? What for?
-不知道  -他没进入主机
- I don't know. - He's not in the mainframes.
看起来他只是想创建一个身份
Looks like he just wanted to create an I.D.
给谁用的身份
An I.D. for who?
法雷尔  马克
中尉
总统先生  亚伦·肖尔来了
Sir? Aaron Shore.
谢谢你  艾娃
Thank you, Ava.
总统先生
Mr. President.
亚伦  很高兴再次见到你
Aaron. Great to see you again.
-我也是  总统先生  -请坐
- You as well, sir. - Please.
早前我在电视上看到你了
I saw you on television earlier.
我真的很感激你说的那番话
I really appreciated what you had to say.
你知道我会一直保护你的  总统先生
You know I'll always protect you, sir.
我知道  所以我才叫你来
I know, which is why I've asked you here.
我将要和你说的事非常机密
What I'm about to tell you is strictly classified.
我们知道白宫里有内鬼
We know that there's a traitor in the White House.
我们一直没能确定他的身份
We haven't been able to identify him,
但我们知道他和国会爆炸案有关
but we know he was involved in the Capitol bombing
而且我被任命为指定幸存者
and was instrumental in having me appointed
他也起到了推动作用
as the Designated Survivor.
你曾是总统里士满的幕僚之一
You were part of President Richmond's staff.
你知道有可能会是谁吗
Do you have any idea who this could be?
这么说不是兰登吗
So, it wasn't Langdon?
兰登已经被关押了
Langdon's in custody.
我们在找的这个人
The person we're looking for
正在销毁此次阴谋的证据
is actively destroying evidence of the conspiracy.
我知道一下子很难接受
I know this is a lot to take in.
但我希望你仔细看看你的记录
But I would like you to go back over your records,
看看有什么引人注意的地方
see if anything stands out.
是  总统先生
Yes, sir.
谢谢你
Thank you.
亚伦  我们时间不多了
Aaron, we don't have a lot of time.
我马上去查  总统先生
I'll get right to it, sir.
他给洛萨诺创建了一个身份
He created an I.D. for Lozano
让他能进入五角大楼
to access the Pentagon.
什么
What?
你得立刻提醒五角大楼保安局
You need to alert Pentagon Force Protection right now.
已经做了  我们把他的照片传了过去
It's already done. We've sent over his picture.
他们正在封锁大楼
They're locking the building down now.
是啊  但五角大楼占地583英亩
Yeah, but the Pentagon's 583 acres.
他有大把地方可以藏身
That gives him plenty of places to hide.
莱纳德先生
Mr. Leonard.
我是汤姆·柯克曼
Tom Kirkman.
总统先生
Mr. President.
请坐
Please.
谢谢
Thank you.
赛斯和我说了你想报道的新闻
So, Seth told me about the story you wanted to run.
总统先生  如果你想劝我收手
Mr. President, if you think you're gonna get me to back down,
那就是在浪费时间
you're wasting your time.
随便你派多少人来盯我
And you can send all the goons you want,
但我绝不保持沉默
but I'm not staying silent.
我不知道你在说什么
Well, I don't know exactly what you're talking about.
我从没派人干过这种事
I haven't sent anyone anywhere.
事实上  我和联调局说得很清楚了
In fact, I've been perfectly clear with the FBI --
我绝不容许恐吓新闻媒体
I will not tolerate any intimidation of the press.
而且很显然  如果我愿意的话
Besides, apparently, if I want,
我可以直接把你送进监狱
I can just throw you in jail.
你是在威胁我吗
Are you threatening me?
不  恰恰相反
No. The opposite.
我是想告诉你  我不会这么做
I'm trying to tell you that I won't do that.
我不会强迫你干任何事
I'm not gonna try and make you do anything.
好吧
Okay.
我是在请求你  拜托先别报道
I am asking you -- please, just hold your story.
你是指报道有误吗
Are you saying it's wrong?
是不完整
It's incomplete.
那不如你帮我补充完整吧
Well...how about you fill in the blanks for me?
我也希望我可以
I wish I could.
遗憾的是  事关国家安全
Unfortunately, it's a matter of national security.
我能问你个问题吗  总统先生
Can I ask you a question, Mr. President?
问吧
Yeah.
如果你手握证据显示现政府有所隐瞒
If you were sitting on a story about a government cover-up,
你还会相信总统所说的话吗
would you trust a word the president said?
也许不会吧
Maybe not.
但你真的相信
But do you honestly believe
倘若总统故意掩盖事实
if a president was involved in a cover-up
他还会蠢到
that he'd be stupid enough
像现在这样与记者面对面交谈吗
to sit across from a journalist such as yourself?
我最敬仰的总统是富兰克林·罗斯福
My favorite president is Franklin Roosevelt.
我想给你看点东西
I wanted to show you something.
你觉得这照片是什么时候拍的
When do you think this picture was taken?
我猜是战时
I expect during the war.
知道它是什么时候公布的吗
Any idea when it was published?
总统过世后
Just after the president passed away.
你看  战争期间有这么一种共识
You see, during the war, there was an understanding --
展现美国的力量
It was more important to project American strength
比报道总统的弱点更重要
than describe the president's frailties.
媒体早就拿到了照片  但他们选择不去报道
The press had the photos, but they chose not to use them.
或许你认为现在并非战争期间
Now, you might not think that we're in a war,
但我可以保证  这就是场战争
but I promise you that we are,
如果你发表了那篇文章
and if you publish that article,
将会让我们更难取胜
it's going to make it that much more difficult for us to win.
我真心希望能把知道的事告诉你  但我不能
Now, I honestly wish I could tell you what I know, but I can't.
所以  就是这样
So...here we are.
你得作出选择
You're gonna have to make a choice --
无论你是否相信我
whether you believe me or not.
科克兰将军
General Cochrane.
你不是来修电缆的
Well. You're not the cable repairman.
退休生活怎么样
How are you handling retirement?
这不是退休
It's not retirement.
这是软禁
It's house arrest.
你让柯克曼别无选择
Well, you didn't leave Kirkman a choice there.
我不怪柯克曼  他做了他应该做的
I don't blame Kirkman. He did what he had to do.
这可不像你啊
Well, that's quite the reversal.
想法是会变的
Opinions change.
你来干什么  亚伦
What are you doing here, Aaron?
白宫里有一个内鬼
There's a traitor in the White House.
我在调查所有拥有高级权限
And I'm looking into anyone with high-level access
并参与了
who had any involvement
选择指定幸存者的人
in choosing the Designated Survivor.
这样的人并不多
That's not a long list.
你能帮忙吗
Can you help?
为什么找我
Why me?
你在白宫任职八年
You served eight years in the White House --
待过国安委  武装部  参谋长联席会议
NSC, military office, Joint Chiefs.
没人比你更了解安全权限的事
No one knows more about security access than you do.
我需要这些系统立即恢复使用
I need these systems back online right away.
五角大楼保卫局  我是鲍威尔
Pentagon Force Protection. This is Powell.
我是联调局探员汉娜·威尔士
This is FBI Agent Hannah Wells.
你们找到洛扎诺了吗
Have you found Lozano yet?
没有  而且我们的安全系统出现了故障
No. And we're having trouble with our security system.
我们所有的监控摄像头都被黑了
All of our surveillance cameras are being scrambled somehow.
但我们在处理了
But we're working on it.
要求传送地址
端口号
我来告诉你一些你们要找的人的信息
Let me tell you something about the man you're looking for.
加入中情局之前  他为五角大楼的
Before the CIA, he worked for the Pentagon for two years
反间谍活动办公室工作过两年
in the Counterintelligence Field Activities Office.
他了解那栋建筑的每一个角落
He knows every single corner of that building.
你们必须让摄像头工作起来
You need to get those cameras up and running.
我们必须找到他
We have to find him.
状态  传送中
完成
我见了科克兰将军
I met with General Cochrane.
他帮我从里士满的行政机构中
He helped me put together this list of staffers
整理出了这份名单
inside of the Richmond Administration
他们都符合我们谈及的条件
that fit the criteria we're talking about --
有高级权限
high-level access,
并参与了选择指定幸存者
involvement in choosing the Designated Survivor.
干得好
Great work.
尽快把这些资料给里特探员
Get these to Agent Ritter as quickly as possible.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
总统先生  我必须要说
Mr. President, I do have to say --
如果没有将军的帮忙我是无法完成的
I couldn't have done this without the General's help.
我觉得他和袭击并无关联
I don't think he had anything to do with the attack.
我也觉得
Neither do I.
正在追踪嫌疑人
In pursuit of suspect,
他正在前往乔治城铁路站场
heading towards Georgetown Rail Yard.
请求支援
Send backup.
这事还没结束
It's not over.
没有牺牲
No victory...
就没有胜利
without sacrifice.
丹尼斯
Dennis!
丹尼斯应该开溜了
I think Dennis stepped away.
知道吗  作为看门人
You know, as far as gatekeepers go,
这里还差了点
there's a lot to be desired here.
我觉得你应该升升级了  赛斯
I think maybe it's time to trade up, Seth.
那么你来吧
You know, you should just move in at this point.
我还是喜欢我现在这样
I prefer the view from my side of the street.
你想怎样  埃布
What do you want, Abe?
我想让你帮我转告总统
Look... I want you to tell the president
他的话我认真思考了很久
I thought long and hard about what he said to me.
我会尊重他的要求
I'm going to honor his request.
但是
But...
不是无限期的
not indefinitely.
我很意外  不知道该说什么了
I'm... speechless. I don't know what to say.
作为新闻发言人这水平可不行
Not the best quality for a press secretary.
那我就说谢谢你吧
Well, l-let me just say "thank you."
也行
That'll work.
千万别以为我这是示弱了
Don't think for a second I'm going soft here.
我还是会给你找麻烦的
I'll still be kicking your ass all over the schoolyard.
随时奉陪
You know where to find me.
汉娜
Hannah.
恰克
Chuck.
天哪  你还好吗
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
我没事
Yeah.
需要我送你
Can I get you a...
去医院吗
hospital?
还是别的
Or something?
他们已经让我出院了
They already checked me out.
知道洛萨诺为什么去五角大楼了吗
Did you guys find out why Lozano was at the Pentagon yet?
希望我们能很快知道答案
Hopefully, we'll get answers soon.
好吧
Yeah.
你需要我留下来吗
Do you want me to stay?
不
No.
不用  法索那边需要你
No, Foerstel needs you.
不过尽快跟我联系
But check in as soon as you can.
好的
Yeah.
以免我忘了  我并没有
Hey, before I forget -- I wasn't...
想故意打探什么的
you know, snooping around or anything,
不过你好像收到了很多电子邮件
but you got about a thousand unread e-mails.
是啊  我一直忙着呢
Yeah, I've been busy.
有一封是杰森·亚特伍德的
There's one from Jason Atwood.
我觉得应该告诉你
I thought you'd like to know.
谢谢
Thank you.
这项行动仍然有可行性
The operation is still viable.
现在  我会清除你
Right now, I'm brooming any connection
布朗宁·里德以及国会任务之间的联系
between you, Browning Reed, and the Capitol mission.
那我想知道
Then I want to know why there were
为什么两名联调局调查员来调查我的物业
two federal investigators on my property.
这你别担心  我会去查
Don't worry about it. I'm on it.
很快  就不会再有书面记录等等的问题
Soon, there'll be no paper trail whatsoever.
而且威尔士探员已被抓获
And Agent Wells is contained.
一切都在按计划进行
Everything is proceeding as planned.
你确定
And you're sure
联调局不会发现任何端倪吗
that the FBI has no idea what's coming?
-控制权在我们手里  -那就好
- We have operational control. - Good.
确保剧情会按照我们的剧本发展
Just make sure that the narrative is what we want it to be.
我们就快接近了
We are so close.
我们也许没有总统地位
We might not have the presidency,
但可以十分肯定  不久以后
but you can be damn sure that before long,
我们就能掌控整个国家
we will have the country.
惠特克先生
Mr. Whitaker.
我们能谈谈吗
Can I have a word, please?
请进
Come in.
亚特伍德副局长
Deputy Director Atwood?
我是汉娜·威尔士探员
I'm Agent Hannah Wells.
对  来自芝加哥
Yes -- from Chicago.
梅里特探员让我告诉你
Agent Merritt tells me to tell you...
他还是很生你的气
that he's still very pissed at you.
长官  我和他的看法不是总能达成一致的
Sir, Agent Merritt and I didn't always see eye-to-eye.
他还跟我说你几乎违背了
He also tells me that you disobeyed
他给你的下达的每一个命令
practically every order he gave you.
不长官  我只违背那些值得违背的命令
No, sir -- only the orders worth disobeying.
他还说  你是他手下最优秀的探员之一
He also says that you were one of the best agents he's ever had,
这也是他对你的离开感到气愤的原因
which is why he's mad at you for leaving.
就像我说的  他是个很棒的上司
Well, like I was saying, he was a-a great boss.
威尔士探员
Agent Wells...
实话告诉我  你会给我带来麻烦吗
in all honesty, will you cause me any trouble?
有可能  长官
Probably, sir.
欢迎来到华盛顿
Welcome to D.C.
我们就快接近了
We are so close.
我们也许没有总统地位
We might not have the presidency,
但可以十分肯定  不久以后
but you can be damn sure that before long,
我们就能掌控整个国家
we will have the country.
就是这样
And that's it.
全部的真相
That's everything.
很抱歉我把你们蒙在鼓里这么久
I am very sorry for keeping you in the dark for so long.
但我别无选择
But I didn't feel like I had any other choice.
希望你们能原谅我
I hope you can forgive me.
我理解  总统先生
I understand, Mr. President.
我也是  总统先生
Same here, sir.
所以是惠特克让你成为的指定幸存者
So, Whitaker made you Designated Survivor?
没错  他以国土安全部顾问的身份
Yes, as Homeland Security Advisor,
手握极佳的政治位置
he was well-positioned
为劳埃德执行了许多行动
to carry out a number of operations for Lloyd.
劳埃德现在在哪
Where's Lloyd now?
我们还在搜查当中
We're still searching for him.
不过作为世界上的头号通缉犯
But as the most wanted man on the planet,
找到他只是时间问题
it's just a matter of time.
与此同时
In the meantime,
联调局突袭了他在全国各地的
the FBI raided cells from his organization
基层组织
across the country.
逮捕了超过二百人
They've arrested over 200 people,
缴获了枪支  制造炸弹的材料
seizing firearms, bomb-making materials,
包括与国会爆炸案中
including explosives --
使用的同一种炸药
the same kind that were used at the Capitol bombing.
赛斯
Seth...
是时候告诉美国民众事情的真相了
it's time to tell the American people the truth.
当然  我会通知各大电视台
Absolutely -- - I'll inform the networks,
确保他们能排出档期
make sure they clear some time.
这次我不想在总统办公室发表讲话
I don't want to speak from the Oval.
我想发表国会演讲  召开联席会议
I want to address Congress -- a joint session.
谢谢你们所有人
Thank you -- all of you.
你们所做的一切
For everything.
回去工作吧
Let's get back to work.
是  总统先生
Yes, sir.
亚伦  我能占用你一点时间吗
Aaron, can I borrow you for a moment?
总统先生
Sir?
你有什么计划
What are your plans?
我还在考虑
I'm still figuring that out.
我想让你回到白宫来
I'd like you back here at the White House.
你属于这里
This is where you belong.
很感谢您的表态  总统先生
I appreciate the gesture, Mr. President,
但是我的职位已经有人了
but... my position is been filled.
而且艾米丽干得很好
And Emily's doing a fantastic job.
我完全同意你的看法
I couldn't agree with you more.
我们会再给你找个职位
We'll find you another position.
说实话  总统先生  没有这样的职位
Frankly, sir, none exist.
那就造一个出来
Then I'll make one up.
亚伦  我想让你在这工作
Aaron, I want you here.
逼急了我拖也要把你拖过来
I'll draft you if I have to.
但我不接受"不"这个回答
But I won't take "No" for an answer.
你觉得呢
What do you say to that?
我很愿意为总统效劳
I say I serve at the pleasure of the president.
很好
Good.
因为从法律意义上讲  我不能把你拖过来
'Cause legally, I actually don't think I can draft you.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
谢谢先生
Thank you, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
今晚准备好了没  要演讲了高兴吗
You ready for tonight? Happy with your speech?
最好是准备好了
I better be.
这次是我自己写的稿
I wrote it myself this time.
我为你骄傲  年轻人
Well, I'm proud of you, son.
今晚坐在那看你演讲
And I'm going to be even prouder
我会更骄傲的
when I watch you from my seat tonight.
我正想跟您谈谈这件事
I wanted to talk to you about that.
说吧
Yeah.
这是那次袭击之后
This is gonna be - the first time since the attack
所有政府成员首次共聚一堂
that the entire government will be under the same roof.
而我要做出
Now I have to make a decision --
让谁留下来的决定
who to leave behind.
你是我心中做指定幸存者
I can't think of anyone I would want more
最合适的人选
to be my Designated Survivor than you.
我以前认为当指定幸存者
You know, I used to think that being Designated Survivor
是一种惩罚  一个玩笑
was a punishment -- a joke.
我也是
Me too.
但现在不是了
Not anymore.
确实不是了
No, not anymore.
这是我的荣幸  总统先生
It would be my honor, Mr. President.
谢谢
Thank you.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
国会成员们
members of Congress,
亲爱的美国民众
my fellow Americans.
我曾在就任总统伊始
At the very beginning of my presidency,
在那个笼罩着恐怖阴霾的重要夜晚
in the shadow of that terrible, fateful night,
与你们讲过话
I spoke to you,
我承诺过执政绝对透明
and I promised absolute transparency,
绝对真实
absolute truth.
但我违背了那些誓言
I betrayed that pledge
为的是保护联调局和特勤局
in an effort to protect an ongoing investigation
正在进行的调查
by the FBI and the Secret Service.
但是今晚  我的心情异常轻松
But tonight, I speak to you with a lightened heart
因为我终于能够把所有事实真相
because I can finally tell you the truth
告诉大家了
about what really happened to us.
最近一位受举国尊敬的记者
A recent article written
写了一篇文章  他说的没错
by one of our nation's most respected journalists was correct.
艾尔萨卡没有袭击我们的国会大厦
Al-Sakar did not attack our Capitol.
即使那个时候
Even though at the time,
大量的证据都指向他
overwhelming evidence suggested just that.
现在我们可以百分百确定地告诉大家
We can tell you now, with absolute certainty,
这场可怕的恐怖行动是由
that this horrific act was carried out
国内的恐怖团伙策划的
by a domestic terror group,
领导者叫帕特里克·劳埃德
led by a man named Patrick Lloyd.
帕特里克和他的朋友认为
Lloyd and his followers believed
伟大美国已经衰落
that American greatness was in its decline
他们认为我们不再是推翻
and that somehow, we were no longer heirs
法西斯主义和成功登月的
to the generations that pushed back the tide of fascism,
那代人的继承者
put men on the moon,
认为我们把柏林墙精神遗弃在历史之中
and relegated the Berlin Wall to the pages of history.
简而言之  这些人相信
In short, these people believed
我们最好的时光已一去不复返
that our best days were behind us
而他们  认为自己更懂
and that they, themselves,
如何重建我们的国家
knew better how to remake our country.
但他们错了
They were wrong --
错的非常离谱
in every possible way.
他们贬低了美国梦
They debased the American Dream and disrespected
践踏了无数个为保卫美国
the incredible sacrifices made by so many
而牺牲的先烈们
to build and sustain our nation.
但就算美国国旗因为他们的
And even though the fabric of America
暴力和仇恨有所磨损
may have been frayed by their violence and hatred,
我也很开心有一个事实是
I stand here rejoicing in the fact
国旗绝不会因此而撕裂
that it was never torn.
即使面临空前的恐惧  我们也没有抛弃彼此
In a time of unprecedented fear, we did not abandon one another.
没有抛弃我们的理想  我们的团结
Nor did we abandon our ideals, our sense of community,
我们的人民
our commonalities.
从在悲剧来临时
From the first responders who answered the call,
接到电话重进火海的急救人员
racing into the flames when tragedy struck,
到那些通过投票来
to the men and women who fulfilled their civic duties
履行公民义务的所有群众
by casting their ballots
即使头顶袭击的威胁
even under the threat of attack,
人民的光芒依旧刺破苍穹
our better angels have shined through.
我知道有时候
Now, I know that there are times
我们的国家显得四分五裂
when our country appears to be divided,
但我能看到有一样东西
but I have seen the one thing
把我们永远联系在一起
that will bind us together forever --
那就是爱
love.
对祖国的爱  对希望和梦想的爱
Love of country, love of hope, love of dreams,
对生命的爱  对自由和追寻幸福的爱
love of life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness.
我是丈夫  是父亲  是这个国家的儿子
I am a husband, I am a father, and I am a son of this nation,
我从未如此骄傲  如此乐观
and never before have I been more proud, more optimistic.
你们不需要告诉我  你们深有同感
And I do not need you to tell me that you feel the same way, too,
因为我能从你们的眼中看出来
because I can see it in your eyes
从你们内心的声音里听出来
and hear it in your hearts.
正如圣·保罗告诫我们的一样
As Saint Paul admonished us,
"我们不要被恶战胜  要以善胜恶"
"Let us not be overcome by evil, but overcome evil with good."
美国不只是一个国家
You see, America is not just simply a country,
不是五十个州的简单集合
nor is it the sum of its 50 states.
美国是一种信念
It's an idea --
一种大胆而正义的信念
a bold and righteous idea,
一盏永不会熄灭的明灯
a guiding light that can never be extinguished.
所以我们要对世界其他国家们说
So let us say to the rest of the world --
我们期待你们的友好
we welcome your friendship and extend an open hand
也向所有寻求自由美好生活的人们伸出双手
to anyone who wants to make lives freer and better.
而与我们为敌的人  我只能警告你们
And to those who oppose us, I can only simply warn you --
你们时日无多了  因为我们的时代来临了
your days are numbered, for our time has come!
我重申  我们的时代来临了
I say again, our time has come.
美国人民们  请允许我说一句
And to the American people, let me say
能为你们服务是我毕生的荣耀
that it has been the privilege of my lifetime to serve you,
我向你们保证  我将继续努力
and I promise to continue serving
直到你们不再需要我为止
until I am asked of service no more.
感谢你们给我的荣誉
Thank you for the honor.
上帝保佑你们
God bless you.
上帝保佑美国
And God bless the United States of America.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你们做的一切
Thank you for everything.
爸
Daddy!
小宝贝
Little pea!
天啊  你怎么来了
Oh, my gosh! What are you doing here?
-李奥  -妈妈带我们来的
- Leo! - Mom brought us.
我实在无法不让他们见你了
I couldn't keep them away any longer.
天啊  我好想你
Oh, my gosh. I missed you so much.
你好美
You look so pretty.
打扰一下  先生  夫人
Excuse me, sir. Ma'am.
怎么了  麦克
What is it, Mike?
需要您立刻到指挥行动中心
You're needed in Command Ops right away.
我保证  马上就回来  好吗
I promise - I'll be right back, okay?
-我爱你  -我也爱你  亲爱的
- I love you. - I love you, too, sweetheart.
马上回来
I'll be right back.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
总统先生
Mr. President.
-稍息  -是  先生
- At ease. - Yes, sir.
什么情况
What's going on?
先生  我们知道洛萨诺
Sir, we know what Lozano
在五角大楼拿到了什么
was accessing at the Pentagon.
他黑进了国防部
He hacked the Defense Department's
最高机密的服务器
most highly classified server.
意味着什么
What does that mean?
意味着国家防御体系的
It means every single aspect
每一个环节
of our country's defense superstructure
都有危险  军队调动
is now vulnerable -- troop movements,
核武器储备  秘密线人的身份
intel on our nuclear arsenal, identities of our covert assets.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我们认为洛萨诺把这些数据
We think that Lozano
发给了帕特里克·劳埃德
sent the data to Patrick Lloyd.
劳埃德可能借此向我们索要赎金
Lloyd could hold us to ransom,
把情报一点点卖给出价最高的买家
sell off the information in pieces to the highest bidder,
甚至自己将这些情报军事化
even militarize the intel himself.
对他的追捕有进展吗
Are we any closer to finding him?
没有
No, sir.
他手上握有的资源
He has the resources to get himself
能让他在不触发任何警报的情况下
anywhere in the world
前往世界任何地方
without setting off any trip wires.